Finding Aid for the Ernst Toch Papers PASC-M.0001
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence, Series 3.
  - Correspondence, 1937 (Apr-Jul) (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Items 84-114. Primary correspondents: AMP, Brentano, Gebhart, Copland, Coolidge.
  - Correspondence, 1937 (Aug-Dec) (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Items 115-145. Primary correspondents: Bermann, Halpern, Tischer, Edington, Doeblin, Copland, Coolidge, AMP, Sinzheimer, Finston.
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Jan-Apr) (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Items 1-29. Primary correspondents: AMP, Edington, Schoenheimer, Berman, Copland, ASCAP, Tischer, Coolidge, Elkans, Beck, Rink.
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Apr-Jun) (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Items 30-59. Primary correspondents: Bernard, Steinfeld, Riesenfeld, Coolidge, Beck, Klein, Reichner, Rink, Sachs, Czuczka.
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Jun-Jul) (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Items 60-89. Primary correspondents: Beck, Rothmann, AMP, Coolidge, Steinfeld, Rink, Weil, Sinzheimer, Riesenfeld.
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Jul-Sep) (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Items 90-114. Primary correspondents: Slonimsky, Thimann, Bernard, Sinzheimer, Beck, Koenigs, Klein, Rothmann.
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Sept-Oct) (Box 39, Folder 5)
    Items 115-137. Primary correspondents: Beck, Sachs, Karpfen, Feilbogen, Coolidge, Slonimsky, Glaser.
  - Correspondence, 1938 (Oct-Dec) (Box 39, Folder 6)
    Items 138-162. Primary correspondents: Steinfeld, Klein, Coolidge, Karpfen, Rink, Beck, Lopatnikof, Heinsheimer.
  - Correspondence, 1939 (Jan-Apr) (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Items 163-193. Primary correspondents: Willner, Chekhov, Brangham, Klein, Prinz Hubertus, Lewis, Rink.
  - Correspondence, 1939 (Apr-Jun) (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Items 194-210. Primary correspondents: Fuchs, Disney, Klein, Karpfen, Dieterle.
  - Correspondence, 1939 (Jul-Oct) (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Items 1-21. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Stokowski, AMP, Schott, Willner, Breitner, Paramount.
  - Correspondence, 1939 (Nov-Dec) (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Items 22-37. Primary correspondents: Jokl, Jacobsen, Heise, Hirscher, AMP.
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Jan-Mar) (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Items 38-66. Primary correspondents: Leonard, Coolidge, Illing, Spiro, Jokl, Kestenberg, Lebeck.
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Jul-Sep) (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Items 95-120. Primary correspondents: Bernard, Reis, USC, Coolidge, Straus, Buchwald.
  - Correspondence, 1940 (Oct-Dec) (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Items 121-144. Primary correspondents: Trotter, Geiringer, Leonard, Barbirolli, Loewenstein, Coolidge.
  - Correspondence, 1941 (Jan-Apr) (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Items 145-178. Primary correspondents: Stokowski, Barbirolli, Feuermann, Milhaud.
  - Correspondence, 1941 (May-Sep) (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Items 179-203. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Schoenheimer, Zwack, Barbirolli.
  - Correspondence, 1941 (Oct-Dec) (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Items 1-31. Primary correspondents: Feuermann, Coolidge, Nathan, Guggenheim Foundation.
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Jan-Mar) (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Items 32-58. Primary correspondents: Korn, Heifetz, Rodzinski, Leonard, Barbirolli.
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Apr-Jun) (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Items 59-86. Primary correspondents: Copland, Coolidge, AMP, ASCAP, USC.
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Jul-Aug) (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Items 87-109. Primary correspondents: Stock, Bass, Coolidge, USC, AMP.
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Sep-Oct) (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Items 110-139. Primary correspondents: AMP, Coolidge, Koussevitzky, Rubinstein, Mitropoulos, Rodzinsky, Kindler.
  - Correspondence, 1942 (Nov-Dec) (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Items 140-175. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Barbirolli, Benswanger, Monteux, Walter, Heifetz, Goosens, Roth, Steinberg.
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Jan) (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Items 176-209. Primary correspondents: AMP, Koussevitzky, CBS, Meacham, Fassett, Feuermann, Caston.
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Feb) (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Items 1-26. Primary correspondents: AMP, Roth, Coolidge, Caston, Koussevitzky, Rodzinsky, Goosens.
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Mar) (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Items 27-61. Primary correspondents: Rosenblatt, Ewen, Goosens, AMP, Steinberg, Coolidge.
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Apr) (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Items 62-89. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Stokowski, Koussevitzsky, E. Power Biggs, Smith, Kallen.
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Apr-Jun) (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Items 90-116. Primary correspondents: Goosens, Coolidge, Sproul, Hutcheson, Kallen, RCA.
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Jul-Oct) (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Items 117-144. Primary correspondents: Kleinsmid, Hermanns, Coolidge, Klkan, Abas, Doeblins, Sinzheimer, Kempner.
  - Correspondence, 1943 (Oct-Dec) (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Items 145-172. Primary correspondents: Kahn, Coolidge, Brentano, AMP, Poddany, Kempner, Ormandy, Rodzinsky.
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Jan-Feb) (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Items 173-198. Primary correspondents: Sinzheimer, Klein, Coolidge, Lopatnikoff, Palmer, Bowen.
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Mar-May) (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Items 1-30. Primary correspondents: Delkas, Kempner, Coolidge, Jacobsens, Fles, Weiskopf, Kaufmanns, Klemperers, Kestenberg, McCarthy.
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Jun-Jul) (Box 43, Folder 2)
    Items 31-61. Primary correspondents: Mann, Olitzki, Liepmann, Fles, Kempner, Balogh.
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Jul-Aug) (Box 43, Folder 3)
    Items 62-93. Primary correspondents: Mitropoulous, Balogh, Kroll, Kestenberg, Petersen, Sinzheimer, Werfel.
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Sep) (Box 43, Folder 4)
    Items 94-116. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Eddy, Kempner, Koussevitzky, Mitropoulos, UCLA.
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Oct) (Box 43, Folder 5)
    Items 117-145. Primary correspondents: Morrison, MacMillian Co., Leonard, Caston, Harvard, Kempner.
  - Correspondence, 1944 (Nov-Dec) (Box 43, Folder 6)
    Items 146-178. Primary correspondents: Eddy, Slater, Coolidge, Fischer, Koussevitzky, Fles, RCA, Appel, Heifetz.
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Jan-Mar) (Box 43, Folder 7)
    Items 179-209. Primary correspondents: Steinfeld, Klein, Schweisheimer, Trowi, Sinzheimer, Slater, Szell, Landau.
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Apr-Jun) (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Items 1-26. Primary correspondents: Rovics, AMP, Coolidge, Gliere, Leonard, Reese, Stokowski, USC.
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Jul-Aug) (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Items 27-55. Primary correspondents: ISCM, Leonard, Balogh, AMP, Sack, Ewen, Trotter.
  - Correspondence, 1945 (Sept-Dec) (Box 44, Folder 3)
    Items 56-90. Primary correspondents: Goossens, Adler, Sack, Cuningham, Lipson, Hecht, Doeblin, Trotter, Schirmer, Holmboe, Landau.
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Jan) (Box 44, Folder 4)
    Items 91-118. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, AMP, Hersholt, Hecht, Kempner, Jacobsen, Wilkins, Beck.
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Feb-Mar) (Box 44, Folder 5)
    Items 119-141. Primary correspondents: Bruel, AMP, Steinfeld, Adler, Thomas, Coolidge.
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Apr-May) (Box 44, Folder 6)
    Items 147-173. Primary correspondents: Ralston, Reis, Steinfeld, AMP, Leonard, Eisenhart, Amlinger, Thomas.
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Jun-Jul) (Box 44, Folder 7)
    Items 174-211. Primary correspondents: Mann, Coolidge, Schott, Cuningham, AMP, Amlinger, Schuman, Zylmann, Steinfeld, Kuhn, Stokowski, Tischer.
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Aug-Sep) (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Items 1-33. Primary correspondents: Schott, Steinfeld, Amlinger, Lunt, Korn, Falian, Cowen, Engleman.
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Sep-Oct) (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Items 34-66. Primary correspondents: Szell, Coolidge, AMP, Pillot, Temianka, Lewis, Amlinger, Steinfeld, Doerr, Zylmann, Chudnow.
  - Correspondence, 1946 (Oct-Dec) (Box 45, Folder 3)
    Items 67-99. Primary correspondents: Hecht, Coolidge, Kuhn, Ewen, Macloskey, Steinfeld, Klemperer, Kirschler, Trotter, Weiller.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Jan) (Box 45, Folder 4)
    Items 100-129. Primary correspondents: Smith, Trotter, Hirschler, Wilkins, Steinfeld, Csonka, Leonard, Schott, Krenek, Tischer, Piastro, Leduc, Amlinger, Kuhn, Adler.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Feb-Mar) (Box 45, Folder 5)
    Items 130-165. Primary correspondents: Tobison, Krenek, Marston, Steinfeld, Katona, Willner, Fabel, Adler.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Mar) (Box 45, Folder 6)
    Items 166-197. Primary correspondents: Csonka, AMP, Smith, Adler, Rauch, Hock, Fabel.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Apr) (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Zoll, Bernard, Scudder, Wallenstein, Goldsen, Koussevitzky, Rodzinski, Goossens, Mitropoulos, Caston, Mendel.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Apr-May) (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Reiner, Krueger, Koussevitzky, Goldsen, Kuhn, Strang, Zylmann, Mendel, Doeblin.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (May) (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Items 51-77. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Zylmann, Schott, Monteuz, Steinfeld, Meyers, Rhodes, Amlinger, Runyon, Robertson.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Jun) (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Items 78-104. Primary correspondents: Tischer, Amlinger, Coolidge, Zylmann, Hock, Keduc, Strecker.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Jun-Jul) (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Items 105-131. Primary correspondents: Criterion, AMP, Elkan, Hock, Tischer, Zylmann, Steinfeld.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Aug) (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Items 132-156. Primary correspondents: Tischer, Kuhn, Amlinger, Coolidge, Schott, Kaum, Steinberg.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Sep) (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Items 157-178. Primary correspondents: Dispeker, Amlinger, Smith, Heller, Doerr.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Sep) (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Items 1-24. Primary correspondents: Cowen, Schlee, Geiringer, Zylmann, Hock, Schoenberg, Fable, Csonka, Lebek.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Oct) (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Items 25-51. Primary correspondents: Universal-Edition, Coolidge, AMP, Criterion, Delkas, Tischer, Csonka, Schnabel, Schnizler, Steinfeld, Spivacke, Doerr.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Oct-Nov) (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Items 52-84. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Schnabel, Criterion, AMP, Chaikin, Zylmann, ALACA, Doeblin, Doerr, Greissle.
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Dec) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Items 85-119. Primary correspondents: Schott, Kuhn, Greissle, Hock, Doerr, Trotter, Strecker, Willner, Zylmann, Stutschewsky, Adler, Jacobsen, Petrillo.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Jan) (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Items 120-154. Primary correspondents: Steinfeld, Dick, Cleveland Orchestra, Itscher, Zylmann, Popper, Aja, Thomas Mann, Webber, Brentano, Slonimsky, Irish, Adler.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Feb) (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Items 155-177. Primary correspondents: Deutsch, Zylmann, Stutschewsky, ASCAP, Randkaer, Reichner, Kuhn, Tischer, Walker.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Mar) (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Items 1-32. Primary correspondents: Holly, Reichner, Goldsen, Turner, Greissler, Winter, Dispeker, Lesen, Coolidge, Leonard, Deutsch.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Mar-Apr) (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Items 33-63. Primary correspondents: Leonard, Wells, Steinfeld, Deutsch, Kuhn, Compinsky, Zylmann, Greissle, Reichner, Goldsen, J.S. Trotter, Stang.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (May) (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Items 64-87. Primary correspondents: Criterion, J.S. Trotter, Primo, Jacobsen, Holly, Eisler, Steinfeld, Trotters, Wolfinsohn, Reichner.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (June) (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Items 88-113. Primary correspondents: Kuhn, Criterion, Helfman, Doerr, Hock, Zylmann, Schott, Wilkins, Wolfinsohn, Deutsch, Klocke.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Jul) (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Items 114-136. Primary correspondents: Aja, Schott, Sunshine, AMP, Criterion, Zylmann, Klemer, Coolidge, Koussevitzky.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Aug) (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Items 137-168. Primary correspondents: Stokowski, Copland, Harris, Schumann, Coolidge, Carlson, Cummings, Mann, Sapiro, Popper, Koussevitzky, Johnson, Einstein, Rosenbaum, Klein, Cowell.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Sep) (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Items 169-201. Primary correspondents: Doerr, Cowell, Winter, Simondet, Marsh, Coolidge, Gunzbourg, Klocke, Zylmann, Reichner, Robertson, Pretzfeld, Szigeti, Tischer, Holde, Merritt, Kalmus, Hitsch, Fabel, Lopatnikoff, Davidovsky, Baum, Milhaud.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Sep) (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Schott, Weschler, Holde, Lopatnikoff, Coolidge, Lubin, Strecker, Downes, Walker, Strang, Steinfeld, Leonard, Ormandy, Kotula.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Oct) (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Items 26-51. Primary correspondents: Ronell, Copland, Croen, Downes, Werfel, Lubin, Slonimsky, Cowell, Smitts, Stokowski, Vega, Leonard, Klein, Rosenbaum, Walker, Doerr, Shaw, Kanitz, Steinfeld, Griller.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Nov) (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Items 52-75. Primary correspondents: Griller, Eble, Coolidge, Rosenbaum, Steinfeld, Cole, Leonard, Holmboe, Werfel, Formigli, Deutsch, Wellesz, Tischer, Mann, J.S. Trotter.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Nov) (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Items 76-99. Primary correspondents: Griller, Kestenberg, Tischer, Downes, Kolisch, AMP, Elkan, Vega, Heifetz, Sinzheimer, Szigeti, Schott, Fraenkel, Kaufman.
  - Correspondence, 1948 (Dec) (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Items 100-125. Primary correspondents: Kolisch, Kalmus, Mann, Kuhn, Coolidge, Webber, Gal, Greissle, Trotters, Cowell, Sendry, Leonard, Zylmann, Holmboe, Wilder.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Jan) (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Clausen, Langlie, Doerr, Kotula, Wellesz, Gal, Webber, Fassett, Langinger, Holmboe, Deutsch, Dispeker.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Jan-Feb) (Box 49, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Strecker, Tischer, Holmboe, Barbirolli, Popper, Gal, Strecker, Langlie, Landauer, Copland, Griller, Waddington, Weintraub.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (March-Apr) (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Items 176-224. Primary correspondents: Tompkins, Fabel, Griller, Coolidge, Strecker, Soyer, Barbirolli, Harris, Fassett, Zylmann, Kolisch, Sinzheimer, Herwig, Brann, Weintraub, J.S. Trotter, Gal, Kolb, Werfel, Wallenstein.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Apr-May) (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Kolish, Sokoloff, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Dispeker, Stuckenschmidt, Coolidge, Ergerinsky, Kramer, Jacobsen.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (May-June) (Box 50, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Sokoloff, Trotter, Toldis, Alma Mahler-Werfel, Barbirolli, Elly Heuss Knapp, Hans Gal, Schott, W. Neurath, Korn.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (June-July) (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Leonard, R.Trotter, Broder, Lebek, Cowell, Holmboe, Viertel, Popper.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (July) (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Kuhn, Tischer, Landau, Kramer, Amlinger, Ormandy, Coolidge, Sokoloff, Rosenwald, Viertel, Nussbaum, Schott.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Aug) (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary correspondents: Popper, Landau, Chasins, Hirschmann, Fabel, Neuman, Viertel, Stillman, Leeds.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Aug-Oct) (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Kaus, Leeds, Landau, Amlinger, Downes, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Schoenberg, Szells, Barbirolli, J.S. Trotter, Coolidge, Steinfeld, Weis, Alma Mahler-Werfel, Schott, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Oct-Nov) (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Schott, Coolidge, Rosenfeld, Meeder, Goldsen, Weis, Leinsdorf, Trotter, McKray, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1949 (Nov-Dec) (Box 50, Folder 8)
    Items 176-214. Primary correspondents: J.S. Trotter, Barraud, Sacher, Mertens, Andre, Viertel, Amlinger, Jacobsen, Alma Mahler-Werfel, Schott, Bass, Zylmann, Marx, Kramm, Scherchen, Seidler, Coolidge, Castelnuovo-Tedesco.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Jan) (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Gruen, Bayerischer Rundfund, Zylmann, Schiske, Litschauer, Marx, Leeds, Manheim, AMP, Viertel, Stolper, ALACA, RIAS.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Jan-Feb) (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Nehammer, Manheim, Schiske, Lindfors, RIAS, Seidler, Pfeffer, Marx, Stolper, Jacobsen, Nahammer, Weis, Seidler.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Feb) (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Tischer, Stillman, Hawkes, Rutz, Stolper, Trotter, Zylmann, Pfeffer, Furtwaengler.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Mar) (Box 51, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Theodore Presser Co, Seidler, Schercen, Furtwaengler, Tischer, Strecker, RIAS, Stillman.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Mar-Apr) (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary correspondents: Seidler, Furtwaengler, Tischer, Strecker, Gruen, Stolper, Avseev, Zoff, Scherchen, Trotter, Brecht, Byrns.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (May) (Box 51, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Strecker, Seidler, Hartmann, Weinberger, Deutsch, Heuss, Byrns, Strcker, Bass, Weeden, Stolper, Haefner, Zylmann, Coolidge, Gram.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (May) (Box 51, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Altmann, AMP, Furtwaengler, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Byrns, Stolper, Munch, Coolidge, Schott, Seefehlner, Holmboe, Laaff, Strecker, Trotter.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (June) (Box 51, Folder 8)
    Items 176-213. Primary correspondents: Seidler, Stillman, Knepler, Mersmann, J.S. Trotter, Stolper, Rink, Brecht, Hartmann, Seefehlner, Haefner, Scherchen, Gruen, Strecker.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (July) (Box 51, Folder 9)
    Items 201-230. Primary correspondents: Scherchen, Gramm, Strobel, Haefner, Rink, Trotter, Rink, Altman, Stolper, J.S. Trotter, Bass, Knepler, Riksskringikasting.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Aug-Sep) (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Items 1-27. Primary correspondents: Harbach, McKray, Kolisch, Hafner, Stolper, Schott, Mahler-Werfel, Rink, Blau, Seidler, Rink-Weeden, Rikskringkasting, Deutsch, Bass, Jacobsen.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Sep-Oct) (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Items 28-55. Primary correspondents: Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Stolper, McKray, Rikskringkasting, Harbach, Furtwangler, J.S. Trotter, Jacobsen, Strobel, Beer, Strecker, Hafner, Zoff, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Oct-Nov) (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Items 56-81. Primary correspondents: Jacobsen, Strobel, Brauch, Leeds, Hartmann, Strecker, Stolper, Coolidge, Hafner, Rutz, Grun, Trotter, Rink-Weeden, Hirshman, Schroeter.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Nov-Dec) (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Items 82-118. Primary correspondents: Lundahl, J.S. Trotter, Mersmann, Tompkins, Seidler, Hartmann, Rink-Weeden, Strecker, Jacobsen, Rutz, Hafner, Schenker, Stolper, Aurelio de la Vega.
  - Correspondence, 1950-51 (Dec-Jan) (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Items 119-146. Primary correspondents: Stolper, McKray, Trotter, Schott, Grete, Loess, Hafner, Byrns, Wilder, Rink-Weeden, Kramer, Brauch, Strobel, Jacobsen, Rutz, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Jan-Feb) (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Items 147-178. Primary correspondents: Strecker, Trotter, Rutz, Brauch, Hafner, de la Vega, Strobel, Rink, Stolper, Harbach, Schroter, Ormandy, Jacobsen, Beer.
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Feb-Mar) (Box 52, Folder 7)
    Items 179-207. Primary correspondents: Frank, Strecker, Trotter, Stolper, Schroter, Korn, Bass, Hafner, Rink, Ormandy, Brauch, Steinfeld, Rutz, Kramer, Seefehlner, Grun.
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Mar-May) (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Items 1-34. Primary correspondents: Schroter, Goslich, Seefehlner, Ormandy, Stolper, Mueller, Jacobsen, Schott, Beer, Temianka, Winter, Kramer, Litschauer.
  - Correspondence, 1951 (May-June) (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Items 35-70. Primary correspondents: Stolper, Schroter, Schott, Kramer, Jacobsen, Kuhn, Bass, Furtwangler, von Karajan, Coolidge, Steinfeld, Hafner, Keilberth, Winter, Grun, Trotter, Rutz, Mahler-Werfel.
  - Correspondence, 1951 (June-Sep) (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Items 71-104. Primary correspondents: Stolper, Jacobsen, Kramer, Rutz, Grun, Strecker, Castelnouvo-Tedesco, Hafner, Trotter, Compinsky, Steinfeld, Zubal, Shilkret.
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Sep-Oct) (Box 53, Folder 4)
    Items 105-127. Primary correspondents: Trotter, von Karajan, Bass, Steinfeld, Grun, Kestenberg, Stolper, Hafner, Bauer, Jacobsen.
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Nov-Dec) (Box 53, Folder 5)
    Items 128-165. Primary correspondents: Leinsdorf, Stolper, Strecker, Compinsky, Steinfeld, Kestenberg, Pilz, Temianka, Kramer, Trotter, Leeds, Coolidge, Winter, Beer, Szell, Barbirolli, Hafner, Jacobsen, Rutz, Harbach.
  - Correspondence, 1951 (Dec) (Box 53, Folder 6)
    Items 166-190. Primary correspondents: Spong, Hafner, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Barbirolli, Strecker, Stolper, Rutz, Beer, Coolidge, Bass, Wallenstein, Tompkins, Stein, Steinberg, Holmboe.
  - Correspondence, 1950 (Jan-Feb) (Box 54, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Kestenberg, Szell, Rutz, Ormandy, Nixon (secretary), Schott, AMP, Kramer, Lopatnikoff, Haefner, Schroeter, Kurtz, Goldsen, Koch, Strecker, Vega.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Feb-Mar) (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Items 26-50. Primary correspondents: Weeden, Beer, Schroeter, Horenstein, Stolper, Strecker, Zubal, Bass, J.S. Trotter, Keilberth, Ormandy, Adler, Zubal, Schenker, Klemperer, Trotter.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Mar-Apr) (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Goldsen, Weeden, J.S. Trotter, Azell, Stolper, Gruen, Strecker, Steinberg, Keilberth, Zubal, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mottier, Compinsky, Coolidge.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Apr-May) (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Steinberg, Stolper, Mottier, Weeden, Goehr, Hilb, Borciani, Strecker, Brengola, Kestenbeg, Rink.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (May-June) (Box 54, Folder 5)
    Items 100-125. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Schotts, Mottier, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Stolper, AMP, Weeden, Veinberger, Adler, Beer, Gruen, Bauer, Hilb.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (June-July) (Box 54, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Coolidge, Stolper, Adler, Petrassi, Rink, Brengola, astelnuovo-Tedesco, Reitz, Byrns, Klemperer.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (July) (Box 54, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Temianka, Borciani, AMP, Koch, Liebermann, Saltoft, J.S. Trotter, Gates, Byrns, Nissim, Reitz, Steinfeld, Leeb, Jacobsen, Mottier, Bass.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (July-Aug) (Box 54, Folder 8)
    Items 176-208. Primary correspondents: Trotter, Bass, AMP, Gates, Hilb, Rink, Steinberg, J.S. Trotter, Schweitzer, Klemperer, Vaughan, Wallenstein, Stolper, Schott, Mottier.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Sep) (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Items 1-25. Primary correspondents: Heuss, Rink, Steinfeld, AMP, Stolper, Treichlinger, Keilberth, Jokl, Bass, Rebner, Temianka, French, Klemperer, Mitropoulos.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Oct-Nov) (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Items 26-51. Primary correspondents: Bauer, KlempererReitz, Nissim, Beer, Hoffman, Klemperer, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Wallenstein, Gruen, Rink.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Nov) (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Items 51-75. Primary correspondents: Hilb, Munch, Fraenkel, Wallenstein, Jacobsen, Axshalamoff, Trotter, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Rozsa, Coolidge.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Nov-Dec) (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Items 76-100. Primary correspondents: Jacobsen, Hilb, Rutz, French, Stolper, Ormandy, Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Trotter, Baerenreiter, Coolidge, Bass, Heuss, Mottier.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Dec) (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Items 101-125. Primary correspondents: Klemperer, Hilb, Stolper, Coolidge, Lopatnikoff, Wilkinson, Trotter, Kramer, Strecker, Reitz, Jacobsen, Hilb, Schott.
  - Correspondence, 1952 (Dec) - 1953 (Jan) (Box 55, Folder 6)
    Items 126-150. Primary correspondents: Kolisch, Munch, Rink, Hilb, Fraenkel, Lopatnikoff, J.S. Trotter, Hirschler, Kramer, Strecker, Bass, M. Mann.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Jan) (Box 55, Folder 7)
    Items 151-175. Primary correspondents: Kramer, Hilb, Rink, Aulich, Strecker, Bass, Kramer, Beer, Hilb, Ormandy, Kolisch, Kramer.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Jan-Feb) (Box 55, Folder 8)
    Items 176-200. Primary correspondents: Steinberg, Levinger, Temianka, Steinfeld, Aulich, Munch, Rink, Kolisch, J.S. Trotter.
  - Correspondence, 1953 (Feb-Mar) (Box 56, Folder 1)